<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on </title>
    <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:58:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ankuroh.com/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiramisu Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 22:59:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Tiramisu is my favorite Italian dessert. It is made with spoon biscuits known as savoiardi; really soft and has coffee flavored taste to it. I have had it multiple times in Italy and still continue to have it in Germany whenever I can. The crux of this Tiramisu recipe is from one of my Italian friends; a few other tiny modifications are from my side. Here is my attempt at surprising by making Tiramisu for some of my dear friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer Chicken Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 13:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Are you an ardent lover of both, beer and chicken? If yes, then this recipe is for you. Initially, I was amused by this idea when my Chinese flatmate was making it by mixing both together. Will chicken cooked with stew made out of beer really go well? However, later, I ended up falling in love with this dish. You are free to replace chicken with any other meat, or tofu or cottage cheese if you are a vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Forest Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This is one of my all time favorite cake. As a kid, I had this cake during my birthdays as well. However, until I came to Germany, I did not know that the cake has its origin from Germany. Schwarzwald translated to Black Forest, an actual mountainous region in the south western part of Germany. Many people including myself would agree that the black forest cake in India differs from the one in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shakshouka Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:53:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I was getting tired of eating things like donuts, krapfens and other sweet things in Europe regularly, and I was looking for breakfast dishes that could be made quickly yet remain at least a bit spicy enough. I stumbled upon a dish called Shakshouka from Tunisia. The variants of Shakshouka are also found in other regions of North Africa and the Middle East. In this blog, I will share this super easy recipe of Shakshouka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boluo Fan Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</guid>
      <description>We all look forward to weekends for different reasons. I was looking forward to this weekend to try some Chinese cuisine. After Googling aimlessly, I came across this dish named Boluo Fan or Pineapple Rice as it is popularly known as in some regions of China and South East Asia. However, every time I come across a Chinese dish, my Chinese friend cross examines the recipe with Chinese websites before giving me a green signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pavlova Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Pavlova is a dessert from New Zealand which my Aussie mate, Ryan, had taught me when we were flatmates in Munich. The dessert sounds very Russian and was indeed named after Anna Pavlova, a Russian ballet dancer, if sources are to be believed. Pavlova is crisp from outside but completely soft from inside. Here is the recipe which I have taken from my friend, Ryan.
Ingredients:  4 eggs Salt 225g caster sugar 1 teaspoon vinegar Half teaspoon vanilla essence 1 dessertspoon cornflour Whipped cream Fruits like strawberries, kiwi, passion fruits, raspberry, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>