<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on </title>
    <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:58:45 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ankuroh.com/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Almond Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/almond-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 09:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/almond-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I baked this cake for my friend on the occassion of her birthday. Given that the birthday fell on a weekday and I was running short of helping hands as well as time, I must admit the effort to make this cake was not much although the result in terms of the taste and aesthetics were pretty decent to celebrate a special occassion. You can give this recipe a shot if you are on a similar boat, or even otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/carrot-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 16:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/carrot-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>My grandfather always tells me there is something to learn from everyone we will come across in our lives. Little did I know that there would be two wonderful ladies, a Turkish and a Kazakh, in my life who would teach me how to bake. They taught me when I was their flatmate in the student dorm in Munich. Strangely, until before this cake, I baked for many people except these two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sichuan Dandan Noodles Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/chinese/sichuan-dandan-noodles-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/chinese/sichuan-dandan-noodles-recipe/</guid>
      <description>If anyone knows me really well, they can assure you my love for Chinese food, especially the noodles with sauce made in Sichuan style. Be it restaurants or other friends, I pounce on the opportunity to ask for Sichuan food if given the option. After eating a lot of times at my friend&amp;rsquo;s place and other restaurants, and watching many videos from other Chinese people on the internet, I tried to replicate one of my favorite Sichuan dishes - the dandan noodles as it is popularly known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donauwelle Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/donauwelle-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 16:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/donauwelle-recipe/</guid>
      <description>When I was a kid, having the famous German black forest cake for my birthday was the norm. After I moved to Munich, Germany, I was only looking for this cake everywhere. However, I could not find it and settled for this thing called Donauwelle. It translates to Danube wave; Danube is a river flowing through different parts of Europe. It has been five years since I had Donauwelle for the first time and it is my favourite cake now; more than the black forest cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/raspberry-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/raspberry-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I love simple cakes made out of different berries and raspberries are one of my favorites. So, here is a simple raspberry cake recipe with toppings of almonds stripes prepared in less than 10 minutes and baked in 30 minutes.
Prep TimeBake TimeTotal Time10 min30 min40 minServingsCal per serving8275 kcalIngredients: 200g flour 70g sugar 8g vanilla sugar 5g baking powder 125g raspberries 100g melted butter 3 medium-sized eggs 125ml milk 25g of almond flakes (optional) Preparation: Mix all the dry ingredients in a bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Chili Oil Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/chinese/chinese-chili-oil-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/chinese/chinese-chili-oil-recipe/</guid>
      <description>There are two kinds of people I have come across when it comes to adding extra oil to their food: the olive oil people and the chinese chilli oil people. I fall under the latter category. I love to add this to my soup, noodles, rice, pizza, or any other crazy things you can imagine. Having been using the one from my Chinese friend always, one fine day, I decided to make some for myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zereshk Polo Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/middle-eastern/zereshk-polo-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/middle-eastern/zereshk-polo-recipe/</guid>
      <description>The Iranian zereshk polo recipe reminds me of the recipes of Biryani and Pulao from countries like India, Pakistan, and Bangladesh. This does not come as a surprise because these regions were heavily under the Persian influence in the past. Unlike many parts of the world where rice is deliberately sticky or overcooked, Iranians want their rice to be rather separated when served. As an Indian, I can testify how tricky this can be as I have myself made Biryani and Pulao many times and it disappoints me if the rice ends up being overcooked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardamom Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/cardamom-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/dessert/cardamom-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>One Friday afternoon I was craving for some cake to have with my tea and decided to make this. I decided to improve this on the fly by adding some cardamom powder with some toppings of almonds and pistachios. So, here is a simple cardamom cake recipe with toppings of almonds and pistachios prepared in less than 10 minutes and baked in 30 minutes.
Prep TimeBake TimeTotal Time10 min30 min40 minServingsCal per serving8275 kcalIngredients: 200g flour 70g sugar 8g vanilla sugar 5g baking powder 2 tbsp cardamom powder 100g melted butter 3 medium-sized eggs 125ml milk 10g of crushed pistachios (optional) 25g of almond flakes (optional) Preparation: Mix all the dry ingredients in a bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemon Blueberry Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/lemon-blueberry-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/lemon-blueberry-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I baked this cake and my friend, Sukanya took charge of the decoration. We baked this for another friend of ours, Phyllis. We followed a mix of different recipes and fine tuned it to our requirements; especially the sweetness level because we do not boast of a great sweet tooth. You can also adjust the recipe below to get rid of the lemon part completely or increase the strength if you like the taste of it like I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cilbir Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/cilbir-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 13:53:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/cilbir-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I love Turkish breakfast and brunches. One of the dishes my Turkish friends introduced to me was Cilbir (Çılbır in Turkish). I made this for the first time when I was stuck in Munich under lockdown due to COVID-19 and was craving for some Turkish dish. It turned out to be really good; worthy of sharing it on my blog too. Cilbir can easily be made with ingredients that we already have at home or available at the supermarket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pad Thai Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pad-thai-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pad-thai-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I was in Bangkok for a Thai kickboxing camp. At the camp, we had a lady who was responsible for cooking for all of us. I approached her if I can learn how to make some Thai dishes from her and managed to get the recipe of Pad Thai as well. This is one of my favorite dishes as it beautifully combines the taste of salty, spicy, sweet and sour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiramisu Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 22:59:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Tiramisu is my favorite Italian dessert. It is made with spoon biscuits known as savoiardi; really soft and has coffee flavored taste to it. I have had it multiple times in Italy and still continue to have it in Germany whenever I can. The crux of this Tiramisu recipe is from one of my Italian friends; a few other tiny modifications are from my side. Here is my attempt at surprising by making Tiramisu for some of my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer Chicken Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 13:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Are you an ardent lover of both, beer and chicken? If yes, then this recipe is for you. Initially, I was amused by this idea when my Chinese flatmate was making it by mixing both together. Will chicken cooked with stew made out of beer really go well? However, later, I ended up falling in love with this dish. You are free to replace chicken with any other meat, or tofu or cottage cheese if you are a vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Forest Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This is one of my all time favorite cake. As a kid, I had this cake during my birthdays as well. However, until I came to Germany, I did not know that the cake has its origin from Germany. Schwarzwald translated to Black Forest, an actual mountainous region in the south western part of Germany. Many people including myself would agree that the black forest cake in India differs from the one in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shakshouka Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:53:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I was getting tired of eating things like donuts, krapfens and other sweet things in Europe regularly, and I was looking for breakfast dishes that could be made quickly yet remain at least a bit spicy enough. I stumbled upon a dish called Shakshouka from Tunisia. The variants of Shakshouka are also found in other regions of North Africa and the Middle East. I confirmed the recipe with a Tunisian friend of mine as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boluo Fan Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</guid>
      <description>We all look forward to weekends for different reasons. I was looking forward to this weekend to try some Chinese cuisine. After Googling aimlessly, I came across this dish named Boluo Fan or Pineapple Rice as it is popularly known as in some regions of China and South East Asia. However, every time I come across a Chinese dish, my Chinese friend cross examines the recipe with Chinese websites before giving me a green signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pavlova Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Pavlova is a dessert from New Zealand which my Aussie mate, Ryan, had taught me when we were flatmates in Munich. The dessert sounds very Russian and was indeed named after Anna Pavlova, a Russian ballet dancer, if sources are to be believed. Pavlova is crisp from outside but completely soft from inside. Here is the recipe which I have taken from my friend, Ryan.
Ingredients: 4 eggs Salt 225g caster sugar 1 teaspoon vinegar Half teaspoon vanilla essence 1 dessertspoon cornflour Whipped cream Fruits like strawberries, kiwi, passion fruits, raspberry, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kit Kat Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/kit-kat-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 13:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/kit-kat-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>One of my good friends, Elena, is always excited for her birthday and in 2018, she asked me to bake her a kit kat cake. I used my favorite chocolate recipe from my baking star friend, Aysun. For the decoration part, my other baking star friend, Sukanya helped me. We managed to accomplish something finally. Here is the kit kat cake recipe below. Give it a shot for your loved one&amp;rsquo;s next birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
