<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://ankuroh.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 16:21:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ankuroh.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jugglers</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/jugglers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 16:21:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/jugglers/</guid>
      <description>Think of it for a moment
We are all jugglers, aren&amp;rsquo;t we?
Always juggling problems throughout life
With no option at all to break free

There&amp;rsquo;s someone out there somewhere
Crippled with a massive debt
There&amp;rsquo;s someone else also somewhere
Reeling through the H1B visa bet

There&amp;rsquo;s someone out there somewhere
Recovering from a painful breakup
There&amp;rsquo;s someone out there somewhere
Struggling to assemble things for his startup</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>तरीका - Tareeqa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/tareeqa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/tareeqa/</guid>
      <description>For people who can read Hindi:
तरीका शायद गलत था पर इरादा सही
तरीका शायद गलत था पर इरादा सही
माफ़ कर दीजिये हमें मोहतरमा
यह रास्ता नहीं आज़माता तोह शायद आप आते ही नहीं
For people who cannot read Hindi:
Tareeqa shayad galat tha par irada sahi
Tareeqa shayad galat tha par irada sahi
Maaf kar dijiye humein mohotorma,
Yeh raasta nahi aazmata toh shayad aap aate hi nahi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 20:51:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>SHORT INFORMAL VERSION  This is just a blog and not a business. There is no possibility to subscribe to this blog or comment on any post. The site has Google Analytics with anonymization function. If you still wish to not be tracked, you can use plugins for your browser. For Chrome: https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/block-yourself-from-analy/fadgflmigmogfionelcpalhohefbnehm?hl=en For Firefox: https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/google-analytics-blocker/ Alternatively, you can also use Duckduckgo to block all trackers and cookies like session cookies or cookies coming from third party sites, if any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiramisu Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 22:59:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/tiramisu-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Tiramisu is my favorite Italian dessert. It is made with spoon biscuits known as savoiardi; really soft and has coffee flavored taste to it. I have had it multiple times in Italy and still continue to have it in Germany whenever I can. The crux of this Tiramisu recipe is from one of my Italian friends; a few other tiny modifications are from my side. Here is my attempt at surprising by making Tiramisu for some of my dear friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Me A Chance</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/give-me-a-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/give-me-a-chance/</guid>
      <description>Give me a chance to not be a dunce.
Give me a chance to be with you once.

Give me a chance to rectify my mistake.
Give me a chance to put everything for you at stake.

Give me a chance to have your head on my shoulder.
Give me a chance to protect you like a soldier.

Give me a chance to cook for you when hungry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The French Kiss</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/the-french-kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/the-french-kiss/</guid>
      <description>I finally reached Paris
I was missing someone dearly
I craved to hold her hands
And adore the 320 meter tall beauty

The city of love as it is popularly called
A few men knelt down on the ground
Expressing feelings to their lady love
Such was the scene all around

A few couples approched me
Requesting me to take their picture
The man passionately smooched his lady</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Venetian Night</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/the-venetian-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/poetry/the-venetian-night/</guid>
      <description>Over an old rickety bridge
Where a canal connects with the sea
Stands a man in Venice
Who is dumbstruck by its beauty

Vintage buildings lined on the streets
Fresh flowers present everywhere
People waiting to board the boats
Aimlessly going here and there

Young couples making love
Old couples walking holding hands
The aroma of the Italian food
Along with performances by local bands

In midst of all these</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Writing</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 20:51:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/writing/</guid>
      <description>A stash of some of my random poems and shayaris.
English 
The Venetian Night
The French Kiss
Give Me A Chance
Jugglers
Hindi 
तरीका - Tareeqa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Whiskey Museum</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 21:59:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</guid>
      <description>I happened to Google about what to do in Dublin and stumbled upon this link from the Irish Whiskey Museum. My friend being from Canada had some knowledge about this domain but I had zero. However, this visit to the Irish Whiskey Museum was completely worth it and I would strongly recommend it even if you are a newbie like me.
My friend and I booked the Early Bird Premium Tour which cost us around €19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guinness Factory Tour Dublin</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 21:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</guid>
      <description>If you ever had beer in your life, chances are high that you have heard of Guinness and/or tried it as well. Whether you are a fan of Guinness or not is another matter but the Guinness factory tour is well worth it when in Dublin. It is a fascinating place for beer lovers or knowledge seekers to know how they manage to do this, the astonishing numbers behing the gallons produced, tons of barley taken into account and what not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dublin to Cliffs of Moher Day Trip</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:58:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</guid>
      <description>One of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most popular tourist destinations is the Cliffs of Moher; a natural beauty spanning around 14km in length and around 200m in height in the west of Ireland. If you are in Ireland, you can easily make a day trip from anywhere given the size of the country. I made a day trip from Dublin to Cliffs of Moher. While you can go in different ways such as car, bus or train/bus, or even cycle if you are adventurous, my friend and I opted to go with Finn McCools Tours booked via GetYourGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland With UK Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Ireland without the need of any extra Irish visa but just a valid UK visa. There seems to be quite a big confusion about whether one can travel to the Republic of Ireland (not Northern Ireland) with a UK visa. A few friends of mine and people online also seemed misinformed about the same. However, a quick Google and some cases online reveal that indeed one can travel to Ireland with a UK visa and without the need of an extra Irish visa under the Short Term Visa Waiver Program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Scraping With Python - Image Scraping</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/web-scraping-with-python-image-scraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 19:38:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/web-scraping-with-python-image-scraping/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will be performing web scraping with Python and beautifulsoup. We will be scraping images of all the megacities of our world as of 2016 from this link: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Megacity
If you scroll down the page, you should come across a table looking like this: We will be scraping the images from the Image column shown in the above picture. To do this, we use the requests library first like shown in the following block of code:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Scraping With Python - Text Scraping Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/web-scraping-with-python-text-scraping-wikipedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 21:38:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/web-scraping-with-python-text-scraping-wikipedia/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will be web scraping with Python and a library called beautifulsoup to learn how to get data from websites online, especially if you have no option to download them in anyway. To do so, we will be text scraping Wikipedia to get the list of megacities in this world. In addition, we will also scrape the images of the city in another tutorial and store it locally in our system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Web Scraping Legal</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/is-web-scraping-legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 22:38:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/is-web-scraping-legal/</guid>
      <description>Is web scraping legal? A lot of people I met asked me this question; some had no idea that they could be breaking some rules if they scrape blindly because they assumed web scraping is always legal. However, the answer to this question is: it depends. Web scraping is not legal always.
You need to go to the website you want to scrape and look at a few things before concluding if you are breaking any rule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate Excel Reports Using Python</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/excel-report-automation-using-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 10:11:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/automation/excel-report-automation-using-python/</guid>
      <description>People working as data analysts/scientists stumble upon requests for reports from different people. While ad-hoc reports are one time thing, reports that need to be sent periodically, be it daily or weekly or monthly, can take quite a lot of time if done manually. Hence, nn this tutorial, I will show how to automate excel reports using Python. The diagram below illustrates a typical excel report automation workflow.
Get Data From Oracle Using Python Let us import the necessary libraries and establish a connection to our database with the necessary username and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get all records in SQL, Python and R</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/get-all-records-in-sql-python-and-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 14:53:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/get-all-records-in-sql-python-and-r/</guid>
      <description> Given a table or dataframe named students as shown below, get all the records from the table or dataframe.
| ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | student_id | student_name | student_city | student_country | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 1 | John | Atlanta | USA | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 2 | Hari | Mumbai | India | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 3 | Ali | Dubai | UAE | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 4 | Jenny | Berlin | Germany | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 5 | Lisa | Berlin | Germany | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 6 | Priya | Delhi | India | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 7 | Wong | Beijing | China | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 8 | Julius | Rome | Italy | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 9 | Alonso | Atlanta | USA | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- | | 10 | Noor | London | UK | | ---------- | ------------ | ------------ | --------------- |  Select all rows using SQL: SELECT * FROM students  Select all rows using Python: import pandas as pd students  Select all rows using R: students  Result: student_id student_name student_city student_country 1 John Atlanta USA 2 Hari Mumbai India 3 Ali Dubai UAE 4 Jenny Berlin Germany 5 Lisa Berlin Germany 6 Priya Delhi India 7 Wong Beijing China 8 Julius Rome Italy 9 Alonso Atlanta USA 10 Noor London UK  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosnia and Herzegovina With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bosnia and Herzegovina with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bosnia and Herzegovina I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Bosnia and Herzegovina without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Croatia and Bosnia and Herzegovina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Croatia With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Croatia with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Croatia I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Croatia without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Montenegro and Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montenegro With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 09:18:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Montenegro with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Montenegro I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany. I traveled to Montenegro without the need of any extra visa and on arriving at Podgorica airport, I was just stamped without any questions whatsoever. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from the United States of America, United Kingdom, Republic of Ireland or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Safari In Dubai</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>I was on my way to Chennai from Munich and I took a long layover in Dubai to catch up with an old friend of mine and explore the city. While my friend and her husband took me around to the city areas, I also managed to crunch in a tour for desert safari in Dubai. The tour lasts for about 4-5 hours and is completely worth it if you want to experience something different instead of just seeing too many buildings and malls in downtown Dubai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer Chicken Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 13:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/beer-chicken-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Are you an ardent lover of both, beer and chicken? If yes, then this recipe is for you. Initially, I was amused by this idea when my Chinese flatmate was making it by mixing both together. Will chicken cooked with stew made out of beer really go well? However, later, I ended up falling in love with this dish. You are free to replace chicken with any other meat, or tofu or cottage cheese if you are a vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Forest Cake Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/black-forest-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This is one of my all time favorite cake. As a kid, I had this cake during my birthdays as well. However, until I came to Germany, I did not know that the cake has its origin from Germany. Schwarzwald translated to Black Forest, an actual mountainous region in the south western part of Germany. Many people including myself would agree that the black forest cake in India differs from the one in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shakshouka Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:53:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/shakshouka-recipe/</guid>
      <description>I was getting tired of eating things like donuts, krapfens and other sweet things in Europe regularly, and I was looking for breakfast dishes that could be made quickly yet remain at least a bit spicy enough. I stumbled upon a dish called Shakshouka from Tunisia. The variants of Shakshouka are also found in other regions of North Africa and the Middle East. In this blog, I will share this super easy recipe of Shakshouka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandas Data Export Comparison</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/data-anaylsis/pandas-data-export-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:21:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/data-anaylsis/pandas-data-export-comparison/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we look at the common data export options in Pandas using Python and compare them on the basis of execution time and storage size. The file formats used for comparison are XLSX, CSV, Pickle and HDF5.
First, let us consider a dataset with more than 1 million records to perform this task. The dataset I am using has the following structure.
&amp;lt;class &#39;pandas.core.frame.DataFrame&#39;&amp;gt; Int64Index: 1009989 entries, 0 to 1034143 Data columns (total 12 columns): FEATURE1 1009989 non-null int64 FEATURE2 1009989 non-null int64 FEATURE3 1009989 non-null object FEATURE4 1009989 non-null object FEATURE5 1009989 non-null object FEATURE6 1009989 non-null object FEATURE7 1009989 non-null float64 FEATURE8 1009989 non-null float64 FEATURE9 1009989 non-null int64 FEATURE10 1009989 non-null datetime64[ns] FEATURE11 1009989 non-null datetime64[ns] FEATURE12 1009989 non-null datetime64[ns] dtypes: datetime64[ns](3), float64(2), int64(3), object(4) memory usage: 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Pickle File in R</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/programming/data-analysis/reading-pickle-file-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 20:27:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/programming/data-analysis/reading-pickle-file-in-r/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I was asked if I could share a particular dataset with some colleague of mine who wanted to test it in an R environment. Although this sounds straightforward, the problem was that the dataset from Pandas dataframe was stored in .pickle format. Now, at this stage, one possible solution was to load it in Python, save it as a CSV file and load the CSV file in an R environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boluo Fan Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/boluo-fan-recipe/</guid>
      <description>We all look forward to weekends for different reasons. I was looking forward to this weekend to try some Chinese cuisine. After Googling aimlessly, I came across this dish named Boluo Fan or Pineapple Rice as it is popularly known as in some regions of China and South East Asia. However, every time I come across a Chinese dish, my Chinese friend cross examines the recipe with Chinese websites before giving me a green signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pavlova Recipe</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:59:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/recipes/pavlova-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Pavlova is a dessert from New Zealand which my Aussie mate, Ryan, had taught me when we were flatmates in Munich. The dessert sounds very Russian and was indeed named after Anna Pavlova, a Russian ballet dancer, if sources are to be believed. Pavlova is crisp from outside but completely soft from inside. Here is the recipe which I have taken from my friend, Ryan.
Ingredients:  4 eggs Salt 225g caster sugar 1 teaspoon vinegar Half teaspoon vanilla essence 1 dessertspoon cornflour Whipped cream Fruits like strawberries, kiwi, passion fruits, raspberry, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</guid>
      <description>There is actually a whole lot of things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia. However, with limited time, I managed to do only some of them which I am listing below.
Visit the State Hermitage Museum Easily one of the biggest and grandest museums I have been to in my life. Given how grand this museum is and so much to see, I feel my 700 Rubles was completely put to good use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint Petersburg Metro Station Art</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</guid>
      <description>Sometime in April 2018, I visited Saint Petersburg, Russia. Although there were many things I liked about Saint Petersburg, one thing that dumbstruck me was its metro stations. In other words, the Saint Petersburg metro station art. I love trains, be it long distance ones across cities or short distance ones within a city. However, the metros in Saint Petersburg, along with other Russian or Soviet cities perhaps, have arts inculcated in the stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulgaria With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bulgaria with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bulgaria I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Bulgaria without the need of any extra visa and arriving via the land border crossing over to Bulgaria from the Romanian side by train. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from Croatia, Cyprus, Romania or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Bulgaria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romania With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Romania with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Romania I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Romania without the need of any extra visa and arriving at the Bucharest airport. I was only asked about the purpose of my trip and the length of my stay at Romania at the immigration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Ankur&#39;s Profile  try{Typekit.load({ async: true });}catch(e){}   (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i[&#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&#39;]=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){ (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o), m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m) })(window,document,&#39;script&#39;,&#39;https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&#39;,&#39;ga&#39;); ga(&#39;create&#39;, &#39;UA-128810519-1&#39;, &#39;auto&#39;); ga(&#39;set&#39;, &#39;anonymizeIp&#39;, true); ga(&#39;send&#39;, &#39;pageview&#39;);     Ankur Sinha Data Scientist / Data Analyst                     Summary   Currently working at Zooplus AG in Munich as data analyst with Sales and Marketing team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/googled13dfff3b894a532/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/googled13dfff3b894a532/</guid>
      <description>google-site-verification: googled13dfff3b894a532.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>