<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travelogue on </title>
    <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travelogue on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:58:45 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uzupis, Lithuania</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/lithuania/uzupis-lithuania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/lithuania/uzupis-lithuania/</guid>
      <description>Vilnius was one of the places which I did not research much before travelling. I just went there trusting the recommendations of my colleagues who hail from the city and another close friend of mine. However, the morning after I arrived in Vilnius, I was trying to plan my day out as to which places I&amp;rsquo;d visit after the guided walking tour, and I came across this place, Užupis. The pictures on the internet did not tell me much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muay Thai Kickboxing, Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/thailand/muay-thai-kickboxing-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 12:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/thailand/muay-thai-kickboxing-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>I always had a fascination to visit the Shaolin Temple in China. One day, while browsing through martial arts camps across the world, I stumbled upon one such training camp for Muay Thai Kickboxing in Bangkok, Thailand. When I was planning my trip to Hanoi, Saigon and Siem Reap, my friend and I thought about making a short stopover in Bangkok just to attend the camp. Both of us have never tried any form of martial arts before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Siem Reap, Cambodia</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/cambodia/things-to-do-in-siem-reap-cambodia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/cambodia/things-to-do-in-siem-reap-cambodia/</guid>
      <description>One may visit Siem Reap for Angkor Wat alone but with the Cambodian government having a rule that one needs to spend at least a night before exiting the country, some travelers may wonder what can Siem Reap offer beyond Angkor Wat. While Angkor Wat alone can take more than a day if you want to dive deep, there are other things to do in Siem Reap beyond Angkor Wat too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day trip from Saigon to Chu Chi Tunnels</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/day-trip-from-saigon-to-chu-chi-tunnels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/day-trip-from-saigon-to-chu-chi-tunnels/</guid>
      <description>Chu Chi Tunnels is easily one of the most fascinating places I have ever visited. Located about 60 km north west of Saigon, this place should be included in your itinerary if you happen to visit Saigon. I went on a tour of Chu Chi tunnels; you can book this tour via GetYourGuide for about 12 Euros only. The tour last for about 5-6 hours including the travel time. My guide, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day trip from Hanoi to Ninh Binh</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/day-trip-from-hanoi-to-ninh-binh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/day-trip-from-hanoi-to-ninh-binh/</guid>
      <description>There are multiple options to venture out of Hanoi. I ruled out Halong Bay because it seems to be a bit too touristic, rushed and dirty, if you want to accomplish it in one day. I left Halong Bay for another time as I wanted to have a relaxed cruise trip instead. Sa Pa was another option but I had limited time as it is quite difficult to do it in one day; usually the trips last more than a day at least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Saigon, Vietnam</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/things-to-do-in-saigon-vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/things-to-do-in-saigon-vietnam/</guid>
      <description>From having good food to checking out some historical places, there are lots of things to do in Saigon, Vietnam. However, with limited time and specific interest, I managed to do only some of them which I am listing below. You can also book guided tours such as this one to visit more places with insights from locals.
Visit the War Remnants Museum The War Remnants Museum is a must if you are into history and politics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Hanoi, Vietnam</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/things-to-do-in-hanoi-vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/vietnam/things-to-do-in-hanoi-vietnam/</guid>
      <description>From having good food to checking out some historical places, there are lots of things to do in Hanoi, Vietnam. However, with limited time and specific interest, I managed to do only some of them which I am listing below. You can also book guided tours such as this one to visit more places with insights from locals.
Visit the Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum Located at Ba Dinh Square, the mausoleum serves as the resting place of the famous Vietnamese leader, Ho Chi Minh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Thai Cooking</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/thailand/learning-thai-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 12:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/thailand/learning-thai-cooking/</guid>
      <description>I sat down on the floor wincing and gasping for breath after an intense session training for kickboxing. Just then, I noticed a lady with a bag of fresh herbs walking towards the kitchen. Despite the excruciating pain, I got back on my feet immediately and followed her.
I knocked on the door and politely asked, “Hello! Are you going to cook something?”
In a strong Thai accent, she responded, “Yes, maybe after fifteen minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambodian eVisa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/cambodia/cambodian-evisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/cambodia/cambodian-evisa/</guid>
      <description>There are three ways to get the Cambodian visa: online, on arrival or by visiting your nearest Cambodian embassy/consulate. I chose the first option for multiple reasons: not wasting further pages on my passport as I have only a few to spare, I did not want to step out of home to go to the consulate or stand in a long queue after reaching Cambodia to apply for my visa on arrival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Whiskey Museum</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 21:59:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</guid>
      <description>I happened to Google about what to do in Dublin and stumbled upon this link from the Irish Whiskey Museum. My friend being from Canada had some knowledge about this domain but I had zero. However, this visit to the Irish Whiskey Museum was completely worth it and I would strongly recommend it even if you are a newbie like me.
My friend and I booked the Early Bird Premium Tour which cost us around €19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guinness Factory Tour Dublin</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 21:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</guid>
      <description>If you ever had beer in your life, chances are high that you have heard of Guinness and/or tried it as well. Whether you are a fan of Guinness or not is another matter but the Guinness factory tour is well worth it when in Dublin. It is a fascinating place for beer lovers or knowledge seekers to know how they manage to do this, the astonishing numbers behing the gallons produced, tons of barley taken into account and what not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dublin to Cliffs of Moher Day Trip</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:58:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</guid>
      <description>One of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most popular tourist destinations is the Cliffs of Moher; a natural beauty spanning around 14km in length and around 200m in height in the west of Ireland. If you are in Ireland, you can easily make a day trip from anywhere given the size of the country. I made a day trip from Dublin to Cliffs of Moher. While you can go in different ways such as car, bus or train/bus, or even cycle if you are adventurous, my friend and I opted to go with Finn McCools Tours booked via GetYourGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland With UK Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Ireland without the need of any extra Irish visa but just a valid UK visa. There seems to be quite a big confusion about whether one can travel to the Republic of Ireland (not Northern Ireland) with a UK visa. A few friends of mine and people online also seemed misinformed about the same. However, a quick Google and some cases online reveal that indeed one can travel to Ireland with a UK visa and without the need of an extra Irish visa under the Short Term Visa Waiver Program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day trip from Dubrovnik to Mostar</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/bosnia-and-herzegovina/day-trip-from-dubrovnik-to-mostar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/bosnia-and-herzegovina/day-trip-from-dubrovnik-to-mostar/</guid>
      <description>In the first half of 2019, I visited the Balkans; Montenegro and Croatia to be more precise. With a lot of free time in Dubrovnik, my friend and I decided to hop over the border and visit a new nation; Bosnia and Herzegovina. In this blog post, we will how to go about making a day trip from Dubrovnik to Mostar.
It is likely that if you are on Croatian soil, you already satisfy the requirements to enter Bosnia and Herzegovina and enter Croatia again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosnia and Herzegovina With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bosnia and Herzegovina with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bosnia and Herzegovina I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Bosnia and Herzegovina without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Croatia and Bosnia and Herzegovina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best places to visit in Montenegro</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/montenegro/best-places-to-visit-in-montenegro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/montenegro/best-places-to-visit-in-montenegro/</guid>
      <description>Montenegro is a little beauty. It is easily the most underrated place I have visited in my travel history of 33 countries at the time of writing this article. Be it the taxi driver, or the hostel receptionist, or a random person on the street, or the lady at local restaurant, people in Montenegro are really friendly. Some of the people I came across are obsessed with Mahatma Gandhi. I went to this place with zero expectations and even thought if 5 days is a tad bit too much to get bored easily but I was wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Croatia With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Croatia with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Croatia I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Croatia without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Montenegro and Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montenegro With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 09:18:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Montenegro with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Montenegro I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany. I traveled to Montenegro without the need of any extra visa and on arriving at Podgorica airport, I was just stamped without any questions whatsoever. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from the United States of America, United Kingdom, Republic of Ireland or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Safari In Dubai</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>I was on my way to Chennai from Munich and I took a long layover in Dubai to catch up with an old friend of mine and explore the city. While my friend and her husband took me around to the city areas, I also managed to crunch in a tour for desert safari in Dubai. The tour lasts for about 4-5 hours and is completely worth it if you want to experience something different instead of just seeing too many buildings and malls in downtown Dubai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</guid>
      <description>There is actually a whole lot of things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia. However, with limited time, I managed to do only some of them which I am listing below.
Visit the State Hermitage Museum Easily one of the biggest and grandest museums I have been to in my life. Given how grand this museum is and so much to see, I feel my 700 Rubles was completely put to good use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint Petersburg Metro Station Art</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</guid>
      <description>Sometime in April 2018, I visited Saint Petersburg, Russia. Although there were many things I liked about Saint Petersburg, one thing that dumbstruck me was its metro stations. In other words, the Saint Petersburg metro station art. I love trains, be it long distance ones across cities or short distance ones within a city. However, the metros in Saint Petersburg, along with other Russian or Soviet cities perhaps, have arts inculcated in the stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulgaria With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bulgaria with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bulgaria I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Bulgaria without the need of any extra visa and arriving via the land border crossing over to Bulgaria from the Romanian side by train. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from Croatia, Cyprus, Romania or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Bulgaria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romania With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Romania with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Romania I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Romania without the need of any extra visa and arriving at the Bucharest airport. I was only asked about the purpose of my trip and the length of my stay at Romania at the immigration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
