<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travelogue on </title>
    <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travelogue on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 17:58:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Whiskey Museum</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 21:59:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/irish-whiskey-museum/</guid>
      <description>I happened to Google about what to do in Dublin and stumbled upon this link from the Irish Whiskey Museum. My friend being from Canada had some knowledge about this domain but I had zero. However, this visit to the Irish Whiskey Museum was completely worth it and I would strongly recommend it even if you are a newbie like me.
My friend and I booked the Early Bird Premium Tour which cost us around €19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guinness Factory Tour Dublin</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 21:58:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/guinness-factory-tour-dublin/</guid>
      <description>If you ever had beer in your life, chances are high that you have heard of Guinness and/or tried it as well. Whether you are a fan of Guinness or not is another matter but the Guinness factory tour is well worth it when in Dublin. It is a fascinating place for beer lovers or knowledge seekers to know how they manage to do this, the astonishing numbers behing the gallons produced, tons of barley taken into account and what not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dublin to Cliffs of Moher Day Trip</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:58:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/ireland/dublin-to-cliffs-of-moher-day-trip/</guid>
      <description>One of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most popular tourist destinations is the Cliffs of Moher; a natural beauty spanning around 14km in length and around 200m in height in the west of Ireland. If you are in Ireland, you can easily make a day trip from anywhere given the size of the country. I made a day trip from Dublin to Cliffs of Moher. While you can go in different ways such as car, bus or train/bus, or even cycle if you are adventurous, my friend and I opted to go with Finn McCools Tours booked via GetYourGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland With UK Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/ireland-with-uk-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Ireland without the need of any extra Irish visa but just a valid UK visa. There seems to be quite a big confusion about whether one can travel to the Republic of Ireland (not Northern Ireland) with a UK visa. A few friends of mine and people online also seemed misinformed about the same. However, a quick Google and some cases online reveal that indeed one can travel to Ireland with a UK visa and without the need of an extra Irish visa under the Short Term Visa Waiver Program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bosnia and Herzegovina With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bosnia-and-herzegovina-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bosnia and Herzegovina with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bosnia and Herzegovina I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Bosnia and Herzegovina without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Croatia and Bosnia and Herzegovina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Croatia With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/croatia-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Croatia with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Croatia I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany and my friend with whom I had traveled had a student visa from Germany. I traveled to Croatia without the need of any extra visa and entered via the land border between Montenegro and Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montenegro With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 09:18:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/montenegro-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Montenegro with Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Montenegro I had an EU Blue Card/Aufenthaltstitel from Germany. I traveled to Montenegro without the need of any extra visa and on arriving at Podgorica airport, I was just stamped without any questions whatsoever. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from the United States of America, United Kingdom, Republic of Ireland or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desert Safari In Dubai</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/uae/desert-safari-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>I was on my way to Chennai from Munich and I took a long layover in Dubai to catch up with an old friend of mine and explore the city. While my friend and her husband took me around to the city areas, I also managed to crunch in a tour for desert safari in Dubai. The tour lasts for about 4-5 hours and is completely worth it if you want to experience something different instead of just seeing too many buildings and malls in downtown Dubai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/things-to-do-in-saint-petersburg-russia/</guid>
      <description>There is actually a whole lot of things to do in Saint Petersburg, Russia. However, with limited time, I managed to do only some of them which I am listing below.
Visit the State Hermitage Museum Easily one of the biggest and grandest museums I have been to in my life. Given how grand this museum is and so much to see, I feel my 700 Rubles was completely put to good use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint Petersburg Metro Station Art</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/russia/saint-petersburg-metro-station-art/</guid>
      <description>Sometime in April 2018, I visited Saint Petersburg, Russia. Although there were many things I liked about Saint Petersburg, one thing that dumbstruck me was its metro stations. In other words, the Saint Petersburg metro station art. I love trains, be it long distance ones across cities or short distance ones within a city. However, the metros in Saint Petersburg, along with other Russian or Soviet cities perhaps, have arts inculcated in the stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulgaria With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/bulgaria-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Bulgaria with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Bulgaria I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Bulgaria without the need of any extra visa and arriving via the land border crossing over to Bulgaria from the Romanian side by train. So, if you are a national of any country with a valid visa or residence permit from Croatia, Cyprus, Romania or any other Schengen countries, you do not need an extra visa to travel to Bulgaria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romania With Schengen Visa</title>
      <link>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ankuroh.com/travelogue/visa/romania-with-schengen-visa/</guid>
      <description>This post explains how to travel to Romania with a Schengen visa or residence permit. I am an Indian passport holder with a residence permit from Germany; at the time of traveling to Romania I had an Aufenthaltstitel (student residence permit) from Germany. I traveled to Romania without the need of any extra visa and arriving at the Bucharest airport. I was only asked about the purpose of my trip and the length of my stay at Romania at the immigration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>